Stand by for a message from Dianthus,
President of Earth and
Rotating Premier of the sun system.
- Barbarella?
- Mr. President.
- Love.
Just a minute, I'll slip something on.
Don't trouble yourself.
This is an affair of state.
What I must tell you
not only is grave...
- ...it's a secret.
- A secret?
Have you ever heard of a
young scientist named Durand Durand?
- Yes.
- Recently, while on a trip
to the North Star, he vanished
into the uncharted regions of Tau Ceti.
But... why is that a secret?
Because Durand Durand is
the inventor of the Positronic Ray.
It's a... It's a weapon.
Weapon?
Why would anybody
want to invent a weapon?
How should I know?
I mean the universe has been
pacified for centuries, sir.
What we know of it.
The trouble is we don't know anything
about Tau Ceti or its inhabitants.
You mean they could
still be living in a primitive state
- of neurotic irresponsibility?
- Precisely.
And if they are, and if they have
learned from this young scientist
the unspeakable secret
of the Positronic Ray,
well, it may give them the power
to shatter the loving union
of the universe.
That could lead
to archaic insecurity, and...
And war.
You mean, selfish competition, and...
I mean war.
- Bloody conflict between entire tribes.
- I don't believe it.
Neither do I,
but we can't take the chance.
- Something must be done.
- Yes,
- and you are the girl who must do it.
- Why me?
Barbarella, I have no armies or police,
and I can't spare the presidential band.
Besides, you're a five-star,
double-rated Astro-Navigatrix.
Your mission then:
Find Durand Durand and use
all of your incomparable talents
to preserve the security of the stars
and our own mother planet.
- How do you read me?
- Straight.
Here is the only known photograph
of Durand Durand in existence.
Age 26, hazel eyes,
a rather handsome fellow.
I don't think I'm gonna
be able to recognize him, sir.
Now, this is a portable
brainwave detector.
Attention. Set your
atom transmitter at 0-3-5.
- Positive.
- Object in transit.
Object received.
When you wish to test
for the presence of Durand Durand,
simply press this contact.
The light will glow
and the alarm will sound.
It has a built-in tongue box.
Here is something you may need.
- It's a weapon?
- For self-preservation.
We borrowed it from
the Museum of Conflict.
That's my good girl.
One day, Barbarella,
we must meet in the flesh.
Thank you, and... Love.
Love.
Armed, like a naked savage.
Alpha 7 to Base, Alpha 7 to Base.
We are leaving the zone
of Solar Attraction in seven minutes.
- Acknowledge.
- Base to Alpha 7 , acknowledged.
Prepare for acceleration
into Temporal Space.
Acceleration into Temporal Space
Continuum now beginning.
Alphy, when do we get to
the Tau Ceti gravitational field?
One hundred and fifty-four hours,
seven minutes, elapses Earth time.
Right.
- Wake me up in 154 hours.
- Confirmed.
Good night, Alphy.
Confirmed.
Deceleration looks in line
Barbarella rise and shine
Prepare to insert nourishment.
End of course in temporal acceleration
in seven seconds.
Alphy, it's Tau Ceti.
- What's happening?
- Magnetic disturbances.
Magnetic disturbances?
Emergency systems.
All emergency systems will now operate.
Our magnetic screens are dead.
Force of magnetic hurricane is 11.9.
Gyrocompass is not,
repeat, not functioning.
- You mean you can't navigate?
- That is correct.
I'll switch it to manual.
What are our chances?
Our present possibilities
of non-destruction
are 0.00002 to ten thousand.
My number two stabilizer
has been damaged.
Where am I?
That's what I was gonna ask you.
Planet 16 in the system Tau Ceti.
Air density 0.051.
Cool weather with the possibility
of stormy precipitations.
Analysis of the atmosphere: terrestrial,
with a slight excess of oxygen.
I count 600,324 molecules
per cubic millimeter.
Well, at least I'll be able to breathe.
What marvelous little girls. Hi!
Do you speak English?
Wait, let me adjust my tongue box.
That must be a galactic five dialect.
But I haven't skied in ages.
But that's Durand Durand's spaceship.
Hi.
Listen, you children, this game is very
amusing, but I think it's gone too far.
I don't want to hurt you.
I just want to ask you some
questions about this spaceship.
Come on, untie me
or I'm gonna call your parents.
That's very sweet, but...
No.
Help!
Stop!
Hello.
Thank you.
No.
I can't understand.
I'd better adjust my tongue box.
Are you all right?
I think so.
Who are you?
I am Mark Hand, the catchman.
And you, who are you?
I'm from the planet Earth.
Tell me, what do you know
of this spaceship?
I know nothing.
It was here when I accepted
the job of the catchman.
- Catchman?
- Yes.
All children must live in the ice
and forests of Weir
until they have reached
a serviceable age.
- Serviceable?
- And then I capture them with my net,
just as you have seen,
and turn them over to the authorities.
I see.
Thank you.
Have you ever heard the name
"Durand Durand"?
I know nothing of such matters.
I live alone in the ice
and forests of Weir,
such is the life of a catchman.
Only in Sogo will you find
the answer to the question you pose.
- Sogo? Is it near?
- It's just beyond that ice deck.
By the way, is that your spacecraft
I saw at the far edge of this lake?
Yes, but I'm afraid there may be
something wrong with it.
See, there was a magnetic storm,
and my stabilizers...
Perhaps I can help. I am not
without experience in these matters.
After all, it is I who must service
and maintain this ice craft.
If you'll allow me,
I'll take you to your ship.
But there's no wind.
Hold on.
What a lovely cabin.
Wind.
I'm so grateful for what you've done,
I hardly know how to begin to thank you.
I'm positive I could get you some sort
of recompense from my government.
I mean, if there's anything you need,
or that I can do, please tell me.
Well, you could let me
make love to you.
"Make love" did you say?
- Yes.
- What do you mean?
You don't even know
my psychocardiogram.
Well, on Earth,
for centuries people haven't made love
unless their psychocardiogram readings
were in perfect confluence.
I know nothing of that.
You asked me what you
could do for me, and I told you.
Well, all right,
but I don't see what good it will do.
- Do you have any pills?
- Pills?!
Oh, never mind. I have some, here.
What is this pill?
It's an exaltation
transference pellet, of course.
- I know nothing of this.
- I see.
Well, on Earth, when our
psychocardiogram readings
are in harmony, and we wish
to "make love," as you call it,
we take an exaltation transference
pellet and remain like this.
Here, let me show you.
For one minute,
or until full rapport is achieved.
I don't care for that.
This, this is what I mean.
This, a bed.
That?
But nobody has done that for centuries.
I mean, nobody except the very poor
who can't afford the pills
and the psychocardiogram readings.
- Why not?
- Because it was proved to be
distracting and a danger
to maximum efficiency.
And... because it was pointless to
continue it when other substitutes
for ego support and self-esteem
were made available.
So... you won't do it?
Well, if you simply must insist,
I guess so.
But I can assure you there's really
no point at all in doing it like this.
Without your... garments, please.
Now, I'll have a look
at your stabilizers.
Since your garment is torn, you may
help yourself to my furs, Barbarella.
I think I have found the trouble.
You may proceed now to Sogo.
It's there you will find
Durand Durand, Jr...
...if he still lives.
Good.
And now, Barbarella,
don't you agree with me
that in some things the
old-fashioned ways are best, after all?
What?
Oh, that.
Yes, I must admit it was
rather... interesting.
Still, I see what they mean
by saying it's distracting.
Are you coming with me to Sogo?
No, I prefer the tranquility of the ice
and forests of Weir.
The life of Sogo is too strict,
and the people too dedicated.
But, perhaps, you'll stop this way again
after you've completed your mission.
Yes, perhaps I will.
Well, good-bye and thanks again...
...for everything.
Oh, it was my pleasure.
Please advise present situation.
You wouldn't understand.
- Stabilizers malfunctioning.
- I've been repaired in reverse.
We're going in.
I'll activate the Terra screw.
Barbarella!
Full operational power
on all subterranean systems.
Forty-five degree ascent.
Quarter-to-half for surfacing.
I gotta get rid of this tail.
- I'm dead.
- No.
Where am I?
We are in the labyrinth
of the City of Night.
Are you an angel?
I'm Pygar,
the last of the ornithanthropes.
How do you do?
- And you?
- I'm from the planet Earth.
My name is Barbarella.
But you're soft and warm.
We're told that Earth beings are cold.
Not all of us.
Oh, my poor spaceship. Look at it.
I'm so sorry.
Pygar, what happened to your eyes?
Oh, I fell during a magnetic storm on
this planet, and was carried to Sogo.
Sogo?
The City of Night,
where the Great Tyrant reigns.
There my eyes were destroyed,
and I was left to perish here
in the labyrinth
where Professor Ping found me.
That's terrible.
Can you really fly?
- No, I've lost the will to fly.
- How awful.
It no longer matters.
It's all in the past.
Pygar, have you ever heard
of the name Durand Durand?
Durand Durand?
Yes, Durand Durand.
He's an astronaut from the planet Earth.
I do not know of such things.
- Perhaps Professor Ping can help.
- Professor Ping?
He is wise in all matters
and knows well the affairs of Sogo.
- Where can I find him?
- He's with the others, eating.
He's there. Professor Ping.
- Professor Ping?
- Yes?
My name is Barbarella.
Tell me, what is your origin?
You have the aspect of an earthling.
You are of female gender, are you not?
That is correct.
- Is that an orchid?
- Yes.
You see, orchids have
very little food value,
and they're extremely difficult
to cultivate in this climate.
It amuses the Great Tyrant to resent the
expense of feeding orchids to slaves.
What kind of place is this?
Well, now, that is Sogo, City of Night,
ruled by the Great Tyrant
and dedicated to evil in every form.
And this is the labyrinth.
All that is not evil
is exiled to the labyrinth.
Look.
Who is that gentleman?
Now, that is one of the
Grand Grotesques.
That's the classic way
of ending life in the labyrinth.
Professor Ping, excuse me,
have you ever heard of a man
called Durand Durand?
Durand Durand, from the planet Earth?
- Yes, indeed.
- He's alive?
- Where?
- In Sogo, no doubt.
I must go there at once.
But as you've seen,
no one may leave the labyrinth.
I have a spaceship,
if I can get it going.
My child, perhaps
I can be of assistance.
Oh, if you only could.
Let me take you there.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Pygar, will you show us the way?
What seems to be the trouble?
Well, I'm not sure, exactly,
but I think it's the stabilizers.
Let's have a look.
Pygar, pen.
Here.
Thank you.
Thank heaven the hypotondical
molecules are undamaged.
- Will it take long?
- Hours?
Days? Weeks?
Who knows.
Genius is mysterious.
But I can't wait weeks.
Pygar...
...you can fly me there.
No, I cannot.
Atrophy of the greater alea muscle.
The angel is aerodynamically sound.
It's all a question of morale.
Well, there is nothing to do but wait.
Pygar, where do you live?
Come. I'll tell you how to lead me.
Just ahead.
- It's a nest!
- Why, yes, that's where I live.
It's marvelous.
I'm glad you like it.
Wait, they're coming.
Help!
Pygar, right in front of you.
No, Pygar, no, to the right.
Now!
What is it?
One of the Black Guards
in the service of the Great Tyrant.
But there isn't anybody in there.
No. The Black Guards are leather men,
they are without fleshy substance.
Pygar, you saved my life.
Pygar?
Py... Oh, Pygar!
Be careful.
Oh, Pygar.
Interesting therapy.
- I've regained the will to fly.
- I know.
Oh, it was...
It was just heavenly.
Can you take me to Sogo?
- But I cannot see.
- I will be your eyes, Pygar.
I do not believe it is possible.
We'd be shot down
by the Black Guard patrols.
Not with my
mini-missile projector, we won't.
Are you all right, Pygar?
Yes, thank you.
I don't like the looks of that.
A little to the right.
Pygar, watch out!
I got him.
To the right.
Up, Pygar, up!
We'll try to hide behind that mountain.
Pygar!
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
Just in time,
my energy box is completely dead.
Are we all right now?
I think so. Excuse me.
We're there.
It's right below us.
We must land in a back street,
for your sake.
To be seen in Sogo with an angel
would be anathema.
Oh, I see.
Pygar, keep your head down.
Oh, my.
We must find something
to hide your wings.
Wait, Barbarella.
Don't be afraid, Pygar.
I sense danger, guard yourself.
There's nothing, I promise you. Come.
Barbarella?
Pygar, wait for me!
What do you want of me?
Hello, Pretty-pretty.
Hello.
Thank you very much.
Do you want to come and play with me?
For someone like you I charge nothing.
You're very pretty, Pretty-pretty.
My name isn't Pretty-pretty,
it's Barbarella.
Have you seen an angel anywhere?
- The strange bird?
- Yes.
What's that screaming?
A good many dramatic situations
begin with screaming.
Pygar?
Pygar, back up,
there's a room behind you.
They're not following.
Pygar, come.
Tell me what that means.
Chamber...
...of ultimate...
...solution.
I don't like the sound of that.
I think we'd better get out of here.
Ye who have chosen to die, be welcome.
To terminate the bitterness of life,
you are entitled to select
from three exciting
and surprising forms of death,
one of which awaits beyond each
of the doors you see before you.
Should you fail to choose,
you will be given to the mathmos.
There is no appeal. Next solution.
- Next solution.
- We'd better take the chance.
Wait!
Oh, thank you very much.
You must come with me.
Tell me, what is your name,
and what do you do in life?
I'm concierge to the Great Tyrant.
I must congratulate you
on your sense of timing.
Oh, no, that wasn't me.
That was so ordained
by the Great Tyrant.
I see. Tell me, what is
that horrible thing under the floor?
That is the mathmos, my child.
The mathmos?
You really are from Earth,
you don't understand?
No.
The mathmos... yes.
Well, you see, the whole city
is built over a lake.
A very curious lake, composed
like you and I of living energy,
but energy in liquid form.
And it watches us.
It is magnetic,
and being positively charged,
it feeds on negative psychic vibrations,
what you would call "evil."
Yes, it thrives on evil thoughts,
deeds and flesh.
And, in return, it gives us
warmth, light and life itself.
But... it has a terrible appetite.
Perhaps you'll see some other time.
Pygar, Pygar!
Don't be concerned, my child.
You'll see him again soon enough.
Now, if you'll just come this way.
There, sit.
I'm afraid you must do as I say.
Sit.
Forward, please.
- Oh, Moxys!
- What?
Look, Moxys, the earthling.
You get her, get her now.
The concierge will never let us.
He always spoils our fun.
Let's try anyway.
- Play with us, earthling.
- You must play with us.
We have lots of dolls.
Good heavens,
what are they doing here?
Well, well,
that's Stomoxys and Glossina.
Nieces of the Great Tyrant,
and very highly favored in our court.
- Why not with us?
- That's not fair.
Hush, it's the Great Tyrant's
turn, children.
- We saw her first.
- Now be good girls.
Come on, Glossina.
Here, come stay by me.
So, my pretty-pretty, we meet again.
You, the little one-eyed wench.
You have a good memory, Pretty-pretty.
Yes, sometimes
I like to go among my people.
Be like them, ordinary.
Evil, as you call it.
So, I am your little one-eyed wench.
I am also the Great Tyrant.
- Well, that's nice.
- It amuses me immensely.
Now, I suppose you are interested
in the whereabouts and welfare
- of a certain party, yes?
- Yes, I am.
I'm here on the orders of the
President of the Republic of Earth.
I'm here to find Durand Durand.
I am not talking about him.
I'm speaking of the angel.
- Pygar?
- Yes, Pygar.
He has escaped the labyrinth. Crime.
He has destroyed
12 of my Black Guards. Crime.
And he dares to deprive me...
...of a pleasure unique in Sogo:
an earthling. Crime.
- Crime.
- Where is Pygar?
You want your fine-feathered friend?
There he is.
Pygar.
Amusing isn't it, Pretty-pretty?
Don't you feel like playing,
Pretty-pretty?
- You can play with us if you want.
- Yes, why not?
Good, Pretty-pretty.
You see, the mathmos is
having its effect on you already.
It's the fumes,
they make one want to play.
- De-crucify the Angel.
- What?
De-crucify him or I'll melt your face.
My face, my beautiful face.
- Stop or I'll shoot.
- Stop, my face.
I warn you.
How dare you endanger my face?
Observe her power buckle, Your Majesty.
Depleted. This weapon
is as harmless as a child's toy.
So, it was a trick, was it?
You should have
saved your tricks for, for...
For the birds, Your Majesty?
Yes! Yes, the birds.
The birds. Give her to the birds.
You must!
Tell me, my fancy, fuzzy freak,
what do you think of
when you make love to Barbarella?
Make love?
I do not understand.
Don't be coy with me.
You're in no position.
If only you had one eye in your head
you would see what a delight I am.
My face, my body.
All my things are a delight.
An exquisite delight.
- What is it you want?
- I shall share my delights with you.
You shall make love to me.
An angel does not make love,
an angel is love.
Then you're a dead duck. Guards!
To the mathmos
with this winged fruitcake.
Come along.
Get inside.
Oh, how darling.
Oh, my...
Help!
This is really much too poetic
a way to die.
Password, quickly.
I don't understand.
You are a political prisoner?
- I don't think so.
- Then you're not one of us?
- I'm from Earth.
- Earth?
Planet of the revolutions.
Will you join our cause?
What cause? Who are you?
I am Dildano, head of the revolutionary
forces. This is our headquarters.
- Long live the revolution.
- The revolution.
Patrol report.
Second level, immediately.
No, take the secret passage.
The door, the door.
The door!
Are you typical of Earth women?
I'm about average.
Tell me, how did I
get out of the bird cage?
Through one of our
secret escape chutes.
We've established several secret
escape chutes throughout the city,
indicated on this map
by these lights, here.
It's for the protection of our group.
I suppose you realize
you've saved my life.
A life without cause
is a life without effect.
I'm sure I could get you a substantial
recompense from my government.
Earth woman, shall I tell you
what I would like?
I think I know.
No. No, not like that.
Like on Earth, on Earth. The pill.
I have the pill.
But...
Couldn't we do it your way?
I don't want to change your traditions.
I'm not a savage.
The pill.
All right.
Five years I've waited
for this experience.
Oh, wait!
No...
Long live the revolution...
My group must...
Hello.
Oh, sorry about that.
My group must have a more...
Where did you get those pills?
Only Earth people know of those pills.
You there, John Paul, what news?
My group must have more weapons
before we can launch an attack.
You'll return to your position and
stand by. You will receive your orders.
Right.
You will receive your orders.
- Long live the revolution.
- Revolution.
The door, the door. The door!
You must tell me,
where did you get those pills?
Did an Earth person give them to you,
a man called Durand Durand?
- That's correct.
- Well, where is he?
He gave me those when he first arrived
in Sogo. I haven't seen him since.
He's assumed to be alive somewhere,
probably in the castle.
Do you have anything I can...?
Of course, one of our secret uniforms.
Thank you.
I was sent here by my government
to find Durand Durand.
Your government... That must mean...
That must mean that you have your
spacecraft and weapons as well?
Well, yes, of course.
I don't like this red.
Would you lend
your equipment to our cause?
Oh, no, I couldn't do that, not until
I've accomplished my own mission.
Perhaps... perhaps
we can strike a bargain.
What do you mean?
Only the Black Queen would know
the whereabouts of Durand Durand,
and she has but one vulnerable moment.
When she's in her
secret chamber of dreams.
Secret chamber of dreams?
Yes. She sleep... She sleeps alone
in a room above the mathmos
surrounded by a wall
of impenetrable energy,
to which she alone has the secret key.
There exists, however, a second secret
key which my agents have located,
and is now in my possession.
You want to discover the whereabouts
of Durand Durand,
I want to capture the Black Queen.
You follow my meaning?
If you really do have the second secret
key, why haven't you used it already?
Because our forces have
not as yet been strong enough.
The capture of the Black Queen has
to be associated with a military coup.
With your weaponry and spacecraft,
this can be brought about.
With the Black Queen in your control,
you can get her to divulge the
whereabouts of Durand Durand.
- Yes, I see.
- Good.
I need six hours to ready my attack.
Well, first we're going to
have to contact Professor Ping
to find out if Alpha 7
has been repaired.
Easily done.
I have a secret radio transmitter.
Secret radio transmitter...
Professor Ping to Headquarters,
Professor Ping to Headquarters.
- Professor Ping to Headquarters.
- No.
Headquarters to Professor Ping.
- Come in, Ping.
- Yes, this is Ping.
- Receiving you loud and clear.
- I have the earthling...
- Barbarella.
- ...Barbarella, with me.
She has offered us the use
of her craft and weaponry.
- Is her craft in good working order?
- Yes, I have repaired the stabilizers,
and the craft is ready for flight now.
- Excellent.
- Thank you.
There is one danger, however.
A Black Guard patrol
has spotted the craft
and may return at
any moment to destroy it.
Good heavens.
I have therefore preprogrammed it
to fly to a place of concealment
outside the labyrinth.
- You're a wizard, Ping.
- It is taking off even now.
There it goes.
Perfect flight pattern.
Our rendezvous point
will be at 1600 hours.
And our password will be...
You mean the secret...?
Exactly.
- Right?
- Right.
Headquarters signing off.
The time is right.
The Queen is in her chamber of dreams.
What about the key?
Ah, the key.
There is the secret key.
Where?
It's invisible, of course.
Only an invisible key
can open an invisible wall.
Where?
My mathmos... The key!
The key.
I have it.
I'll put it around your secret neck.
It's invisible.
Now... now, the secret map that will
lead you to the 12th corridor.
Twelfth corridor?
Good.
This way.
- Long live the revolution.
- Revolution.
One moment.
I'm just not the tube type.
Excuse me, could you tell me
how to get to the 12th corridor?
I have a taste for you.
- What is it?
- Essence of man.
- Essence of man?
- Yeah.
Well, well, so you escaped the birds?
Just as well.
Now it's my turn for some amusement.
Come with me.
This way, please.
- What is this thing?
- You will soon see, my dear.
Sonata for executioner
and various young women.
It's...
It's sort of nice, isn't it?
Yes, it is nice, in the beginning.
Wait until the tune changes.
You may change your tune as well.
Oh, goodness.
What do you mean?
When we reach the crescendo,
you will die... of pleasure.
Your end will be swift
but sweet, very sweet.
What's this? I don't believe it.
It couldn't be.
Wretched, wretched girl!
What have you done
to my excessive machine?
You've undone it! You've undone me!
Look, look!
The energy cables are shrinking.
You've turned them into fagots!
You... You've burned out
the excessive machine.
- You've blown all its fuses.
- My goodness.
You've exhausted its power.
It couldn't keep up with you.
This is incredible.
What kind of girl are you?
Have you no shame?
Shame, shame on you.
You'll pay for this.
I've got something in store for you.
You'll wish you had died of pleasure
before this day is done.
Now you shall learn
the wisdom of the lash.
Oh, please,
haven't you done enough to me?
I'll do things to you
that are beyond all known philosophies.
Wait until I get my devices.
Durand Durand?
So... you recognized me?
Recognized you?
I could never have recognized you.
I thought you were only 25-years-old.
What happened?
Well, the mathmos
is not without its effect.
But you've aged 30 years.
The mathmos has its own
means of nourishment,
and in return it teaches us truth.
Dr. Durand,
could you hand me a garment?
I have been sent here by the
President of the Republic of Earth,
hopefully to save you and to
bring you back to our own Earth planet.
Earth planet? Never.
Shall I tell you why?
Because I know too much.
Here in Sogo,
I have learned truth and essence.
I speak of the dignity,
the nobility of pure evil.
Would you hand me some boots?
Humanism, morals, principles.
It's rubbish, nonsense.
I speak only of truth and of essence.
What have you
done with the Positronic Ray?
- So, that's it.
- What does it do?
All persons and objects in its path
are deminimalized to the fourth level.
- You mean...?
- That's right.
They're placed in the
fourth dimension irretrievably.
- But that's monstrous.
- Yes, it is, isn't it?
Why haven't you used it
to take power here in Sogo?
The Black Queen
must first be destroyed.
But, as you no doubt observed, she is
always surrounded by her Black Guards.
Whoever succeeds in killing her will be
put immediately to a horrible death.
Hence my prudence.
I find horrible the idea that one could
do to me that which I do to others.
But I was told that the Black Queen
was vulnerable while she sleeps?
Oh, yes. There are no Black Guards
in the chamber of dreams.
They're not needed there because
there's no access to the chamber.
But, now it's time for my pleasure,
and your death.
Wait.
I know how you can enter
the chamber of dreams.
You? How?
- Speak.
- I have the key.
- What does it look like?
- It's invisible.
Then you really do have the key.
I'll give you five minutes.
Take me to the chamber of dreams.
After you, Barbarella.
To the right, Barbarella.
Now to the left.
Stop.
Open it.
- This must be the invisible wall.
- Yes, now where's the key?
- Come on, come on. Stop stalling!
- I'm trying to find the keyhole.
No.
You're trapped!
Trapped in the chamber of dreams.
The mathmos will devour you.
- Your Majesty!
- It's no use. I've got the two keys.
The wall is sealed for all eternity.
Dr. Durand, will you
give up this madness?
Come back to Earth with me
before it's too late.
Yes, I will return to Earth...
...as its conqueror.
Thanks to you, the queen, the last
obstacle to my plans, has been removed.
Thank you, Barbarella.
Nothing can stop me now.
Today, master of Sogo.
Tomorrow, master of the Earth,
master of the galaxy,
master of the universe!
Tell me, my fine, feathered friend,
what do you think of
when you make love to Barbarella?
An angel doesn't make love,
an angel is love.
Wake up, Your Majesty!
You must wake up!
Vade retro, Earth girl.
I know you don't really exist.
That may be, Your Majesty,
but we'd better stick to what we see.
Wretched girl, what have you done?
No one must enter while I sleep.
Your concierge
is taking over the throne.
What? What are you saying?
It's true, and he's taken your key.
- We're locked in, Your Majesty.
- The key, he's stolen the key.
We're doomed... Doomed!
He said the mathmos will devour us.
What did he mean?
It is said that unless
I am alone in my chamber of dreams...
...the mathmos will claim me.
It's the Throne Room.
I'm able to see into every
part of the city and the labyrinth.
Unfortunately, it's a one-way screen.
No one can see that
that bloody dog has locked me in.
Your Majesty! Your Majesty,
we're under attack!
The creatures in the labyrinth,
they're revolting, Your Majesty.
How dare he interrupt my coronation?
Dispatch the air armada.
Quick, Your Majesty, the labyrinth.
It's Dildano. He will save us.
Your Majesty, they're all destroyed.
Oh, good.
Not a creature left in the labyrinth.
No aircraft left.
They have Earth weapons.
Fool, liar, idiots!
Must I do everything myself?
- I'll destroy this rabble.
- He's gonna use the Positronic Ray.
It works!
It works, it works!
All is lost.
I must die.
Very well, but it is I
who shall have the last laugh.
The imbecile doesn't know
the secret of the Great Tyrant.
The supreme weapon.
- I shall free the mathmos.
- Do you think that's wise?
Sogo will disappear.
It will be the end, the apocalypse.
- Where are we?
- In the mathmos and alive.
I can see that, but why?
It seems the mathmos
has created this bubble
to protect itself from your innocence.
That's nice.
Oh, no. Stop! I command it.
I'm Durand Durand.
I'm the master of the mathmos!
Fall back!
Fall back...
...or I'll destroy you
with my Positronic Ray.
You are so good,
you made the mathmos vomit.
Pygar! What have you done to Pygar?
He was sent to the mathmos, but I see
he's no more digestible than you are.
You can't be dead.
You win, Barbarella, but the Earth
has lost its last great dictator.
The genius of the Positronic Ray.
Why don't you give him
a mouth to mouth?
I have a better idea.
Please. Pygar, please.
Please, wake up.
We must fly back to my spaceship.
Do you have the strength?
Pygar, what did you save her for,
after all the terrible things
she's done to you?
An angel has no memory.